Marcio Nogueira de Lima

46 years old

Married / (1 Son)

Contacts

Address:

Sarandi, Paraná. Brazil.

Phone:

+55 (44) 99930-2641

Email:

marciolima76.ml@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marci o-lima-45077376/

Portifólio:

https://marciolima76.github.io/portifolio/

Languages

Portuguese – Native Speaker English – C2 Italian – A1 Spanish – A1

Hobbies

- Reading
- Codding
- Languages
- Music

Summary: Working as a teacher of English since 2009, as Returned from an experience in England, where lived for three years. With three graduations (Bilingual Executive Secretary, Modern Languages (Portuguese and English), and Analysis and Systems Development) have also taught several subjects in technical courses and worked as a Coordinator.

In 2020, started working from home and became an online teacher of English. Also started learning Computer Science in order to increase his knowledge and to get more opportunities to work at the Educacional and Technology areas.

Experiences:

• Teacher of English, 2023 -present.

DevEnglish – School of English for IT professionals

• Teacher of English, 2020 –2022.

New Age Academy – School of English (Callan Method on line).

• Teacher of English, 2015 – 2018.

MSI School - (New English Life - Oxford Method). Maringá - Paraná.

• Post Office Agent 2014 - present.

EBCT (Correios do Brasil)

• Teacher of English, 2013 - 2015.

Discovery Callan Method – English School, Maringá, Paraná.

Teacher of Portuguese and English, 2010 - 2014. Primary, Secundary and Professional Education School Sarandi and Maringá, Paraná, Brazil.

Education:

• Analysis and Systems Development

UniFCV. Maringá – Paraná – Brazil (2020 – 2023).

- Degree in Modern Languages (Portuguese and English) Unicesumar, Maringá – Paraná - Brazil (2014 – 2017).
- Educational Formation in Teaching

UEM, Maringá - Paraná. - Brazil (2014)

• Postgraduated in Higher Education Teaching

Uniasselvi, Maringá- Paraná - Brazil (2012-2013).

• Graduated in Bilingual Executive Secretary

Unioeste, Toledo, Paraná - Brazil (1995-1998).

International Certifications:

• Cambridge ESOL - University of Cambridge, Bracknell and Wokinghan College, England – UK (2006-2008).